ああ、わかった。
今日はインターネットの接続が少し悪いので、ダウンロードはできません。
1秒。
今日は本当に静かにしていなければならない。   ええ、そうですね。
こんにちは、みんな。
えっと、
それが
ハローカ
ハローです。
皆さんお元気でお過ごしでしょうか。 今日はできるだけ
静かにしようと思います。
ルームメイトが寝ているので、
あまり迷惑をかけたくないんです。 ええ、
できる限り静かにするように努力します。 だから、
私が話している最中でも、私が声を上げることは迷惑ではありません。
音声の状態はどうですか？
ブーストする必要があるか、それとも単に教えていただければ
いいですか？
コンプレッサーを追加してみます。
私はボーカルコンプレッサーを持っています。 私はただこうするだけです
。
うーん、低いですね。 わかった。
入力を
ミキサーに切り替えます。
どこですか？   2つ
目の
ミックスで。 はい、どうぞ。 音声が
遅くなってしまい、きちんと聞き取れません。 持続する
。
これで私の声は十分に聞こえるはずですよね
？
えっと、2分後に音量を調整します
。   はい、どうぞ
。 もっと大きな声で話すべき時が来た。
どうやら私のマイクの音量は27%だったようです。
なんてこった？
ええと、わかりました
。  100%。
すべて順調のようだ。 ええ、そうですね。
えっと、私の声が聞こえるようなので、このまま続けたいと思います
。
えっと、
今日は「
Pu
Champions」というゲームをプレイします。 日本では、Pu
Peu Esportsとして知られています。   えっと、
私は日本にいるので、私のSteam
バージョン、私のSteamリージョンは日本です。
えっと、どうやら
昨日知ったんですが、
このゲームはNintendo Switch
とPS4とコンソール、それに
NintendoとDSでも発売されているんですね。
このゲームはDS版もあります。 うん。
任天堂のゲーム機版の場合、
日本では東アジア地域向けに「Pew Pew Esports」という名称で販売されています
。 でも、そうですね、
今はもっと普遍的になっています。 だから、ある
意味、たとえ日本にいても、
西洋版や
ユニバーサル版をプレイして、
他の日本人や
世界中の音楽とマッチングすることができるんです。 そう、だから、同じ
ものを持っている人たちと一緒に遊ぶことができるんです。   ええ、そうですね。 えっと、
あなたは本当にささやくのが上手ですね。
本当に？ わからない。
えっと、
それで、えっと、
どこまで話しましたっけ？
私がささやいていると思わないでください。 私はまだ
話している。 私は、えっと、もっと話すのを控えないといけない。
いいえ、私はもっと静かな方です。
私はマイクの近くにいます。 ねえ、
ささやき声で話したい？ ささやき声。 私なら
これくらいできると思う。
抑制をオフにできるってどういうこと？   電源を
切ることができます。   え、
私にもできるの？   わかった
。 まだ聞こえると思いますが、
今はどうですか？
これは
rosのようなものです。   何てことだ
。 でも、これは
声みたいなものだと思う。   えっと、
ゲームに切り替えさせてください。 わかった。
もし他の人の
声が私のマイクから聞こえたとしても、無視してください。
ルームメイトたちです。
えっと、こんにちは。 そして、YouTubeで
エビを見ている人たちへ、ええと、そうしてほしいんです
。 昨日、ある人物が
このサービスを発見した。
えっと、ちょっと
探してみますね。 コマンドを追加する必要があります
。
Stream snipe.com。
はい、その1つです。
リンクをコピーしてYouTubeチャットしてください。
正しく貼り付ければいいだけだ。
配信開始まで少し時間がかかっています。
私の名前は既にアクセスされています。
待って、私がささやいても聞こえないでしょ
。 何？ ああ、そうそう。 えっと、なぜ、なぜ、
なぜ生の声がないのですか？   聞こえますか
？ おお。
おい、あの
mはどこだ？
みんな待たせてるぞ。 ごめん。 ごめん。
技術的な問題がいくつかあります。
YouTubeから動画を切り抜いて保存できるようにしてほしいだけなんです
。たとえそれができなくなってしまったとしても。
実際にクリップできる外部サービスがあります
。   では
、少々お待ちください。 ちょっと調整させてください。
待って。
ええと、YouTubeで感嘆符のクリップを作ればうまくいくよ
。   わかった
。   まずは
ゲームから始めましょう。
交代させてください。 ああ、気にしないでください。 えっと。
えっと。
私は実際にゲームを起動して、設定などを済ませておく
ので、
設定とかそういうことを気にしなくて済むんです。
えっと、
私が今ライブ配信中だってアナウンスした？   そうじゃなかったよね
？   では、そうさせてください
。 わかった。
試合の音が聞こえますか？
あなたならできると信じています。
あの、コメントを見せていただけますか？
コメントが表示されません。 こんにちは。 それでは、メニューです。
つまり、このゲームは基本的に
アニメ版テトリスみたいなもので、可愛い感じのゲームと言えるでしょう
。 これらは他のテトリス
ブロックで、1、2、3、5
色だと思います。 ええと、ほとんど4つですね。
ゲームモードによります。 ゲーム
モードに5色設定がある場合は、このように5
色が表示されます。
えっと。
ああ、それは違う。
おい。 えっと。   えっと。
今日は
練習だけをします。   そうします。それから、
2つやりたいです。 私はします
。 よし、やろう。 持久力。
待って、
これらはぷよぷよで入手できるすべてのキャラクターです
。
アミット・アミー・T・リンゴを手に入れました。 彼女はまさに
リンゴみたいだ。   では、
彼の名前はどのように発音するのでしょうか？
リュウイ・
リナ・
アリ・ラグナス。
これが
今日私が演じるキャラクターです。
えっと、魔女のドラコ・サントレス。
えー、リシュ、リシュカ、
キャランゴ、
ダークプリンス、バットマン、そしてアレックス。
アレックスって言おうと思ったんだけど、まあ、だいたい同じくらいかな
。 こんにちは。
えっと、
イヤホンはどこ？ あの、
試合の音は聞こえますか？ うん、
試合の音が聞こえるよね？
こんにちは。
えっと、これは何ですか？
ドローンを素早く地上に降ろす。
背景ブーストが欲しいな。あぁ、あれって
今やテトリスそのものだったのを忘れてた。
ゲームのやり方は全く分からない
けど、うん、できるよ。
ええ、それはできますよ
。 うん、
私ならできるよ。 うん。
えっと、
それは、ああ、連鎖させたくなかったんだ
けど、まあいいや。
ああ、それは鎖だ。 私はそうしたくなかった
。 なぜ？ くそ。 大丈夫です。 大丈夫です。
いや、いや、いや。 上部について説明できます。
大丈夫です。
えっと、
プレイすればするほど、
白いやつはゴミみたいなものだってことが分かるんです
。 ええと、
そうですね、ただそれを調和させて、
それらを一緒に参加させる必要があるだけです。 そこが問題なんです。
あぁ、
これなくしちゃうかも。   チェーンで繋いでください
。 いいえ。わかりました
、それで大丈夫です。   なんてこった。 私は
死ぬと思う。   なんてこった。   なんてこった。
何だって？ 私たちにはチャンスがある。   わかった
。 私たちにはチャンスがある。 はい。 私たちには
チャンスがある。 こんにちは。
私たちにもチャンスはある。 たぶんそうだと思う
けど、
話せない。 これは一種の
コンティニュアスゲームです。 うん。 しかし、
私はそんなつもりはなかったのです。 でも
（泣きながら）
私にはできません。
Windowsには
AIによるノイズ抑制機能があることに気づいた。   だから、何を
待つ必要があるのか​​？   わかった
。   より
優れたもの。
うん。
はい。 最初のチェーン。 それはすばらしい。 それは
すばらしい。
私はそうできます。 わかった。   私ならできます。
そして、これについては、
それを叩いてそこへ行けば、緑はそこへ行くことができます
。
ああ、その繋がりは理解できる。   どうすれば
いいですか？   それも
有効です。 えっと、それを受け取って。 よし、それを手に
入れろ。
あなた自身を開放してください。   中で
倒れたのは知っています。 わかった。 そこを開けて、そこを
片付けてください。
実際、スペースは確保できると思います。   いやいや、そうじゃない。ああ、ほぼそうだ。
アイデアがあるんだ。こうすればできるし、ああすればできる。そして、あれが
来て、それで
プレイヤーが行く。それから、あれをやって、
そこに落とす。
黄色が必要です。
ええ、そうなんです、彼らもそうするし、それが
満たされて、つながるんです。
ああ、
数え方を覚えなきゃ。
カウンターは作っているのですが、
直線を描く方法がわかりません。
ええと、鎖、それが私が探していた言葉です
。
外国人 ああ、
私は死にかけている。 私は死にかけている。 私は死にかけている。
シンダス。
ああ、そんな風に私を殺さないで。   そんな風に
私を殺さないでください。   なんてこった。
自分。
えっと、えっと、
彼女はちょっと、
ああ、いや。 いや、いや、いや、いや、いや。
えっと、何が
必要なのかというと、
ああ、あれ、ああ、待って。   私は
推測する。 わかりました
。
ええと、わかりました
。 そうしてください。
ああ、このゲームを初めてプレイしたけど、
すごく濃密だ。
だから、集中すれば3連鎖も簡単にできる時もあるんです
。   でも、でも、
大金持ちになるのは難しいと思うんです。
私がCPUを相手にプレイしていることを忘れてはいけません
。
もし私が現実の人間と遊んでいたら、
とっくに死んでいたでしょう。
実際の人間が抱える問題。
来る。
私はフィールドをクリアできますか？ そうそう。
片付けを始めたよ。 それはいいです。
えっと、
今夜はサブで演奏できますよ。
ああ、わかった。
ああ、いやいや、間違いじゃないよ。   わかった
。 戦え、戦え、戦え。
ああ、これは楽しくない。 なんてこった。
いいえ。私は死んでいます。
[泣き声]
ああ、YouTubeのチャットが機能している。
何だって？
えっと、ちゃんと
動いてますか？ ああ、うまくいってる。
YouTubeのチャット機能は正常に動作しています。   うまくいっていることは
何か
？
ああ、私は死んだ。
ゲームをプレイする。
そう、このゲームは
私とは違って頭の良い人向けなんだ。
私はFPSとか何でも得意なんです。   だから
私は
頭を使うゲームが苦手なんです。
[笑い]
ああ、そうそう、どうやら
私はプイプヨの
トーナメントに参加することになったんだ。それは
ヴァコーネが主催するヴァコーネ・
ゲーミング・フェストの一環として行われるトーナメントなんだ。 つまり、これはぷゆVTuberクラッシュ
インド競技トーナメントです。
自分のチームが誰なのかは分かりませんが、
このゲームをプレイして、
ゲームが上手なプロや、
ゲームを学んでいる人たちと競い合うことになると思います。
たくさんプレイすることで上手くなった。 だから、
練習してベストを尽くしたいですね。
発熱とは何ですか？
フィーバーは、
もっと速いペースの
会社だと思う。
それでおしまい。
そして、そうしてください。
ええと、大丈夫です。   片付けてください
。 私たちが片付けます。
彼らは何を
食べるのですか？
ああ、これで2件の
衝突だ。 うん。
実際、私の言っていることは正しい。
それと、
このゲームの所有者が誰なのか教えてください。
一緒にプレイしたい場合は、
チャットでお知らせください
。
ああ、大変だ
[叫び声]
ああ、なんてことだ。
えっと、それじゃあ、私は
Yを知らない、それは私、ちっちゃい、ちっちゃい、ああ、くそ
。   それができる
全てです
。
いや、それは結構です。 うん。
ええ、できますよ。 はい。   いいえ。ええと。
熱。
ああ、
[泣きながら]あれは
ひどかった。
ああ、わかった
。
それ。
ああ、
いいね。
いいえ、大丈夫です。 私たちはそこから立ち直ることができる。
私たちはそこから立ち直ることができる。 ええ、
そこから立ち直れますよ。
ええと、それで何が開けるのでしょうか
？ 可能です。
うん。 だから、
私にはこれはできません。
じゃあ、そこへ行こう。   ああ、これだよ
。   そうすれば、
そこに緑色が手に入っただろう。 ああ、
大丈夫です。 それはいいです。
銀行を青くしましょう。
大丈夫です。 なんてこった。
私はそれを解決しました。 私が掃除しました。 良い。
実は、ちゃんと掃除したんです。   何てことだ
。 とんでもない。 完全に失敗してしまった。   とんでも
ない。 完全に失敗してしまった。 私は
そこから立ち直れる。 はい。 うん、
いろいろ考えなきゃいけないね。 私は
こういうゲームが苦手なんです。
おお。   なんてこった。
いや。いや。いや。いや。いや。
ああ、いや。 違う、違う、違う、違う、違う、違う、ああ
。
それでは、これをやります。
それで [泣きながら]
今度は違う。
ああ、兄さん、私はそれを台無しにしてしまったのか？   ここに
来て。 ここに来て。 来る。   ごめん
。
日本は寒いので、風邪を引いてしまいました。
ええ、そうですね。
そうそう。 うん。 私は回復できる。 私は
回復できる。 私は回復できる。   私は
回復できる。   ええ
、それが欲しいです。 はい。
自分。
えっと、それは仲間だよ。 私はそこから立ち直れる
。 ええ、必ずそうします。 彼は
熱を出した。 なんてこった。 なんてこった。
彼は熱を出した。 なんてこった。 いや。いや。いや。
待って。 できます、できます、できます。
ああ、いや。   なんてこった。
K9。  K9。  K9。  K9。 これは
まずい。 これはまずい。 これはまずい。   あの
、
いいですか？ いいえ、回復は不可能です。 ああ、くそ。
Y
mina。   ええ、ええ、ええ、ええ、ええ、ええ、
緑が来ることを信じています。   それを下ろしてくれれば、
私もそれができます。
あぁ、
そこで終わってもよかったんだけど。 それでいいんです
。 えっと、ちょっと片付けなきゃいけないんです。
うん。 うん、それでいいよ。 作品。 作品。
作品。 作品。 下げてよかった。
そして、
このようにしてきれいにすることができます。
そして、あの
熱。
そして、私たちはこのようなことを実行できる。
それが悪い点だった。 それはまずい判断だった。   よし
。   なんてこった。
ええと、そうしてください。   ええと、そんな感じのことはできます
。
持ってこい。 私は黄色をプレイしていて、
ええと、
私はこれとこれを行うことができます。
それで、えーっと、あそこの
赤いやつをやって。
ああ、熱だ。 わかった。 ええと、熱があります。 熱があるんです。
[泣きながら] やってしまった。
熱を下げてしまった。 大丈夫。 その仕事。   わかった
。 黄色。
ああ、大丈夫です。 大丈夫です。
私たちはそこから立ち直ることができる。
ええ、私ならできます。
私たちの手と、
そう、それが私が望んでいたものです。 それから、
全体をクリアしてから、それを行います。 そして、
青いものがやってくる。 では、
ここに置いておけばいいでしょう。
掃除することもできたけど、このままでいいよ。
それは簡単だ。 赤いものがやってくる。
これは
そこでうまくいきます。
ああ、わかった
。 熱。 ええ、できますよ。
うん。   わかりました
。
しかし、最後の調整が問題だった。
ああ、しくじった。
行く
と
首が痛いんだよ。 何てことだ。 少し横にならせてください
。
そんなことはしないでください。
ああ、それはうまくいった
。
それでいいんです。 そして、それで青空が晴れる。
そして、私にはそれができる。 そして
ゲートは、もう一方の
手で勝つことができる。
そして、それを掃除します。   そうしてください
。
バカ、バカ、
バカをいくつか手に入れた。
くそ。   何てことだ
。 どうしてあんなに失敗したんだろう？
どうしてあんなに失敗したんだろう？
ええ、できますよ。 この地域で。
ああ、わかった、
それでいいよ。
そして、私たちにはそれができる。   片付けてください
。   片付けてください
。 それは清掃されます。 そしてそれも
清掃されます。   それはできません
。 ああ、大変だ。
大変なことになった。
熱があります。 よし、それは良いことだ。
熱が出たから良かった。 私には
これは無理だと思う。
以上。
私はそれを台無しにしてしまった。  [泣きながら] 私は
大丈夫、回復できると思った。
このゲームはすごくストレスが溜まるし、
終わりがない。
それは
それと共に歩むことになるでしょう。
えーと、えーと、
おもちゃを手に入れました
。   えっと。
ああ、兄弟。 いいえ。あなたを取り戻せます。 私を見ていてください
[泣きながら]
ああ、兄さん、私はベンチに座っている。   ああ
、ベンチに座っている。 くそ。   ああ
、あれはすごかった。
[ため息]
よかった。
うん。 さよなら。 さて、
アレックス、実際のプロ選手って何なの？
なぜ誰もいないのですか？ リプレイ
スタイルの
クリエイタールームまたは
接続を確立してください。
こんにちは、応援効果。
カウントダウン時に自動再生が開始されます。 ああ、戻ってきて
アシストしてくれ。
同じ予測だ。
これは何ですか？
待って、なんで私は行くの？
セットカウントって何ですか？
お金のウサギを設定する。
えっと、
プロプレイヤーに負けるってどんな感じなのか、私にはわからないんです。
ああ、しまった、自分の位置情報が表示されてる。
ええ、でも今はみんな私がどこ出身か知ってますよ
[笑い] 私は良いところに住んでいます。   あれこれあれこれ
。
こんにちは。
ああ、
今夜。
待って、なんで誰もプレイしてないの？  [鼻を鳴らす]
遊びたい。
なぜ誰もプレイしないのか？   わかった
。
[鼻を鳴らす]
なんで誰も遊ばないの？
ええ、
また
マッチメイキングでチームメイトが必要になりますね。 えっと、
スキル評価。
えっと、部屋の暗証番号を入力しないといけないんです。
え、どうやってやるの？
自分の部屋の暗証番号などはどうやって知ればいいですか？
バック
コレクション。
ああ、いいよ。 キャンセルします。 あ、誰かいるみたいだ
。 誰かが現地で任務に就いている。
えっと、D。グレースJと一緒に行きたい。
よし、私が負けるのを見る時間だ。   ああ、なんてことだ、
魔法のブロックだ。
でも、
彼を真似してみようと思う。 わからない
。   ああ
、なんて速い演奏なんだ。 なんてこった。
ああ、クイックドロップはここにはない。 ああ、そういうことか
。
ああ、くそ。 ああ、だから、だから
。 ああ、彼は本当に素晴らしい
プレーをしている。 ああ、本当にごめんなさい
。 えっと、
兄弟、私には無理です、無理です、できません。
これは、これは、
彼は最速でプレーしています。
私は時間をかけてじっくりやっています。
ああ、くそ。 ああ、あなたのお尻、あなたのお尻、あなたのお
尻。   なんてこった。
ああ、パニックになってきた。   なんてこった。   なんてこった。
おい、[笑い]
おい。
おい、彼の画面で何が起こっているんだ？
Y.
一体何が起こったんだ？  [笑い]
彼は大規模な連鎖反応を起こしたのか？
ああ、なんてことだ、彼の走りを見て。   自分より
強い相手に負けるって、こういう気持ちなのか？
ああ、神様、彼はさらに兵士を送ってくる。 敵
軍。
おお。
おお。 彼の演奏の仕方は、まるで
チェーンのようなものだ。   おい
、やめろよ。 停止。 停止。 停止。 停止。
停止。 停止。 停止。 停止。 停止。 兄弟
兄弟。 兄弟。 チル。 チル。 なんてこった
？
なんてこった？
なんてこった？   理解できません
。
すごくゆっくり演奏してる。 彼の走りを見てごらん。
それは始まった。
それは始まった。 私は死にかけている。 私は死んだ。
[泣き声]
兄弟。
Brother,
he was like, "This guy is not worth it.
V.
What?
Let's go with this guy.
Tokyo. Someone's from Someone from
Tokyo.
Oh god. Japanese players are so pro at
this game. I I can I can I can feel it,
bro. Look at him play. I'm going to get
shit on. Yeah.
N is dead.
The way he's playing systematically like
a pro, it's it's coming to my brain.
Oh no, I'm dead.
Itsyhe
brosy.
It has begun. It has begun. It has
begun. The massacre has begun. Oh, it's
behind. Oh, God. Help me.
Oh my god. What is going on? What the
hell, brother? What the hell?
Oh my lord.
What?
Why?
Let me copy him. Ah shit.
It's
yooy
stop.
I feel like he knows that I'm a easy
target easy player.
Um
a has begun.
Yeah,
bro. What's the point to play? He's
[crying]
Oh my lord.
How do you know how to play the the way
he plays? just like a pro player. The
way he plays is a pro player. Why?
He knows. Hello.
The way he plays is he knows how the
game game works.
It's
perfect.
Oh, bro. Stop massacring me.
Look at that.
Ah, bro.
Oh my. It we we going more. Okay.
Yeah, I know. I lost three times.
Oh, bro. He started to massacre me.
Mate, mate, mate, mate, mate. I'll
massacre him. I can do this. I can do
this. I can do this. I can do this. I
learned the I learned the tactics. I
learned the tactics. I learned the
tactics. I learned the tactics.
Um, yeah, I learned the tactics. Oh my
god, I'm getting better.
Oh fuck. No.
No. [laughter]
I did.
How?
Wait. Let me copy him. Let me copy what
he's doing.
Uh, he put it like this, right? Okay.
Then he put it like this again. Then he
put this thing like this. Okay, let me
copy him. He will not. No.
Uh, okay. Where did he put this? Uh,
no. That was wrong. No.
[snorts]
Ah, yada. I did it wrong. No.
Aha, bro. I couldn't copy him in time.
The massacre has started again.
Uh, yada.
Uh,
bro, I've lost
[crying]
Okay. I I actually did a
combo. I I did a combo. I did a combo.
Oh my god. I did a combo.
Am
I am I so
I feel like if I'm being forced to play
with the with this pro player, I will
improve cuz I'll be like in my Oh, I
actually defeated him. Bro,
I actually defeated him. Okay.
Oh my god. Actually defeated him. Oh my
god. Thank you.
Oh no, no, no, no, no,  no, no.
Bro, stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
She's done.
What?
I got cooked. I got cocky. That's why
I got cocky.
Wait,
what am I doing?
Oh shit.
I got cooked.
Ah,
how do you use your brain to think ahead
in time?
Uh
I uh
oh the breath shit.
Let's
go back. Ow.
Ah.
Yeah.
Hen players.
Okay. Okay.
[crying]
[snorts]
This guy is from Tokyo, right?
Ah,
I didn't want to.
Okay, I do that. Maybe this.
Oh, no, no, no. I can put it there. And
then maybe I can put it like this. Uh, I
can put it there. Okay. Maybe that goes
there. And uh, no, I didn't want to
shit.
Uh, I can go there. And uh,
that works. Okay. Uh, yeah.  He's uh,
he's he's attacking. He's attacking.
He's attacking.
Uh yada yada yada yada.
I can block him maybe. Uh maybe maybe
bro.
Nah.
How do I How do I do emotes?
Is it Is it going to go forever?
Oh my god. It's gonna go. I mean, it's a
good practice [music] dish.
Getting cooked every single time like
this.
It feels not [laughter] It doesn't feel
bad.
Got the shield.
Yeah. I didn't want to
Oh my god, he's attacking me strong.
I'm kind of understanding that you're
not supposed to chain it in the early
stage. You're supposed to do it in the
medium middle stage.
Oh my god, I died.
At least I got one win. Okay.
Yep.
I'll move only when he had Oh shit.
Uh
Jokix, you're too late.
[crying]
Yes, I defeated him. Let's go.
Oh  my god, too. Okay.
Uh, so you have to just match the
colors.
This is good training, by the way. I'm
glad I got a pro Japanese player.
Okay, I almost Oh shit,
he's uh he's on attacking.
Then I'm going to attack him. Knee.
I need one more. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Yes.
Yes. No. No. I was so close.
[crying]
[snorts]
Back to lobby.
H.
Thank you for Oh, he left. Fuck.
I got cooked. How did I Wait, this guy
is still here.
Everyone margin
rate three.
Will he play with me?
Hi.
This ranked in this game.
You can compete in the leaderboards. Oh,
it's Sonic.
Oh shit, I didn't mean to do that. Okay.
Taa.
Ah, that was so dumb.
Oh, it has begun. It has begun. It has
begun.
It has begun. Oh god.
Don't worry.
I'm going to  get you, bro.
Uh, he's he's going to go on attackive.
Oh shit. I still have a chance. I still
have a chance.
Still have a chance.
I still have a chance.
Give me right. Give me right. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes.
I've improved, brother. Yes.
Yes. Yes.
I did it. I didn't let him combo
mass combo me.
I did not let a mouse combo me.
Oh shit, that was that was dumb. That
was dumb. Okay, jump.
Good.
It's
itsy
I'm defeating him.
Yes. Oh my god.
Um
Oh my god, guys. Are you seeing this?
Yay. Yay. Yay. Yay. Yaba yaba. I'm
getting better.
Are you witnessing
Mina?
Uh,
it's it's
I think this was a mistake.
I shouldn't have cleaned it out. I
shouldn't have cleaned it out. Gosh,
that was a  mistake. He He got He got
this round.
He got this run.
Oh, he got this run. I was early. I was
early.
Oh shit. Fuck.
Nice job, bro.
Uh
yeah. Hey
Bro, what am I doing?
Don't let him combo. Don't let him
combo. Do not let him combo.
Do not let him combo.
If you let him combo, you're dead.
Ah.
Shinda shinda.
I let him combo.
H. Oh god. Oh god. I
The way looks like I think I'm going to
die.
Yeah,
black.
It's
Don't overshoot it.
You can now.
I will shoot him. Yeah,
it's fine. Do it.
Do it.
No. Oh, wait. I think I got it. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No.
This guy is so strong.
Seven chains.
He left.
Am I the only one here?
Hello, welcome
worldwide.
Just dropping by here
by all.
What are you uh what is this game about?
It's It's like Tetris but with a with
like some cute characters.
Yeah, it's literally [music] Tetris and
Candy Crush. Similar to that you
um
match color match actually stuff and do
it.
So there is a tournament hosted by Vak
India on 18th of October on a Sunday at
7:30 p.m. ISG. So I'm participating in
that tournament. So I'm like um
practicing
for this.
Yeah.
I know it is here.
We put broadcast to
Can we watch other people?
Let's watch this guy.
Is it recording though?
Look at these guys. The way they are
playing though.
pop to make a fortune.
Look at him play.
How do you know where to target
the prediction though?
Is it?
Oh my
good lord.
guy's a pro.
There's a prediction thingy on
there. That's a prediction thingy on.
That's why I think
I kind of old time, huh?
I kind of understood.
I'll explain the CP version.
Um,
is there anyone  here? Wait,
someone is here in the room.
Oh,
someone from Ku
Japan.
Holy lord. That's a
I've been krah.
He kicked me. What the hell,
bro? He kicked me.
What the hell?
He That guy kicked me. The hell did I do
to him?
I going to
uh And
there are no people in the fever.
Oh.
Oh shit.
Tik Tok. Someone from Tik Tok. [snorts]
Yuru. It's a Japanese brother.
It's
quick.
Or should I die?
It's it's
it's
Itsy
itsy.
Oh no.
It's
Oh shit.
Oh, no.
It's It's
It's
no
He got free points. Rang up.
Oh, my rating went down. Shit.
Fore!
Foreign!Foreign!
Yahoo!
It's
not
Bro, what the hell?
Oh my lord,
I died.
I have to defeat him. How
Uh
it's
Itsyhe
It's
shit.
It's It'sy.
No. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
I just need a It's one v one. No. One
one.
Oh god. He's He's speeding up. He's
speeding up. Yono
quiet.
Oh god,
he's sending threats at me. Oh lord.
It's
a bro.
Brother in Christ.
He
my rating is lowered.
I don't want to play with him.
The hell
filters.
Oh my god.
Oh my, I just played with the top top
number four player in the world.
A grandmaster
who just No, no. Earlier the Gohan guy
was the grandmaster. Oh my god.
How do you say it?
Okay,
replay is the best.
Yeah,
it's secret.
It's
Oh shit.
I didn't even fuck
It's great.
Itsy
item.
Oh no.
Ah,
he won.
One more.
Oh no. What?
Oh shit.
Broch.
These players are crazy
and I'm having a really bad cold.
It's weather. The  weather is so cold,
too.
Stop sending threats,
bro.
No.
Hello, Vic. Oh my god, it's Dick. Hello.
How are you doing?
It's been a while.
How you doing, Rick?
I couldn't do that. Okay.
Uh
oh, he's sending attacks at me. Oh.
Oh my god. Wait. I don't know.
Uh,
please, please, please, please.
No. [crying]
Um
what idle stuff and then I'm fine. This
is okay.
We also doing well. It's uh cold over
here.
What's the weather in Japan right now?
20°.
Cold.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
[crying]
He dropped me.
Ah, he dropped it.
Connection. I think he all that Ford.
What the hell? He's like, I don't want
to play with the newbie.
I need to learn how the game and play
the game.
Let's watch this
tutorial.
Hi
Ready?
Special controls.
Even faster way to drop your sensor is
basically
they  call this quick drop.
Jesus.
This is the chain and they send me the
keys to mushroom field.
I just score a chain score more points.
I found the jeans also some go
up to disappear James
T.
Oh,
simultaneous clear. Oh,
neutralizing.
We call this new choice.
What do you do?
I put that. Oh, okay.
You can neutralize them before.
Oh.
Oh,
okay. That is neutralizing.
Quick one
wrong. If you quickly press the right
person ZX control key twice can rotate
the P.
Oh,
interesting.
It is false.
You can score bonus points. Oh,
saving up chains.
couple of few pure drops ending up here
for easy chains. Okay.
Okay.
Huh.
That's the end of the intermediate.
Creating multiple chains is the key,
too.
Oh, bro. This is so hard.
Okay,
come on this side.
Wait,
is there no one else playing this game
today?
If there people playing, I would want to
play and battle them.
I have to learn how to do this. Bro, at
this point, I don't think I can
win the tournament or the  team. I will
be a disappointment for my team. I mean,
and this is day one though. But I think
I just have to keep on playing and
playing and um understand
the game.
We'll eventually get it.
Um,
one second. Let me check. Uh,
if anyone from
is anyone I know streaming
dish
like
Oh, wait. As first room filming.
Oh, wait. What time is it for people?
Ah, it's 8:00 p.m. for them. Um, it's 12
for me. I forgot Japan time and Indian
time is
uh different
times on
most people get uh start their stream at
10 or 9.
Little battle.
Learn to make chains. That's the
victory. That's the goal to victory.
Learn to make chains. Talk next.
Got to make them chains.
Uh,
Oh shit.
Oh, no. No, no, no. I I was trying to
combo. Come on. I was trying to
I was trying to combo.
chat.
See if you
Interesting.
Shit.
Itsy
didn't do it.
Uh
something like uh
I'm not trying I I'm not supposed to try
to clear it. I'm supposed to build up
chains. Don't forget
build up chains. Dark legs.
Yes. Keep going.
Keep going. Learn how to build up
chains. That's how you'll
understand.
Uh
uh. What the
I need space.
I can defeat him. Yeah.
Yeah. That's how you do legs. Yeah.
Good, good, good, good, good. Yeah.
Yeah. Slow and steady wins the race
slowly.
Surely
I'll try to play this game tomorrow. No,
not tomorrow. I want to play some FPS
tomorrow. Yeah, I'll try to play this
game on weekends.
Uh, no, on weekdays.
Oh, yeah. Monday I don't have class.
Yeah. Uh, so I can find some time. I
need to find some time to tournament.
Oh no. Oh, he's attacking. He's
attacking.
Let me just kill him fully.
I'll just kill him.
Okay, good. Oh my god. I And I I learned
[music] the game. No, wait. No, no.
Don't be cocky.
Take it slow.
Oh shit.
Could have fuck
it.
I can actually do it.
It's about doing, you know, I'm not
supposed to do it early.
Feel like I'm doing the early combos,
which is bad. I have to wait for my
opponent.
Yeah, I'm trying to do a early
stuff that is wrong.
Oh my god, my
uh
Oh god, he got in.
Okay.
It's
slow and steady.
Itsy.
Oh shit.
No.
[crying]
Oh, I might have messed up.
I made a mess up.
Okay, I think we can do one last game
and I can wrap up. It's It's going to be
It's It's 1 It's going to be 12:30.
Yeah, I
I know I could keep on playing, but um
yeah,
sure. I know tomorrow  is a Sunday.
And yeah, for those who don't know, I
Well, I think I didn't tweet. Oh, I
forgot. So, um, for those who didn't
know, my cycle got stolen recently.
So, I'm buying a new cycle bicycle
tomorrow
at 10 in the morning. Um, so after I get
my cycle and stuff, I think I'll start
streaming.
Um, I'm thinking of streaming. Um
um
the thing is when during weekends,
right, I won like some have like a
shooter game. I need my FPS pew pew.
But lately I've been pew pewing so much,
right?
So, I was thinking
um I was thinking I could uh go with
either this game for like 6 hours, six
or eight hours.
Not that long, but it's a Sunday, so
might have to go out to buy stuff
[gasps]
uh and stuff. I I don't I do not know my
schedule for tomorrow. I don't even
think I can do like more than 4 hour
shrimp, but
even at nights I my roommate
uh and I we um he will help prepare the
dinner and
uh by 9 or 10 I I'll get free if he is
going to
uh go sleep early.
So,
um
I could stream from 10 like today's
stream from 10 to 12,
but
yeah, short streams are pain.
[snorts]
Also, I just noticed
I noticed something.
The game goes quiet when you are all
tabbing.
Why is it that?
Why is it like that?
It was windowed.
Does it act the same? Ah, it does.
Uh,
wait. Why is it like that? Oh,
wait. Why is it like that?
Why is it like that?
Okay. Is there a way I could
Let me check. uh for you for your
champions
game.
Is there a way to
uh
when I'm not
focused?
Uh mute window lo
and focus loss is actually for the game.
Uh,
is there a way I could
do something?
Um,
virtual desktop.
No, it
it's doesn't
have audio on
wireless.
Wait
full screen windowed to how do I make it
like have audio
has a hardcoded for mute build directly
in the game engine. Oh.
[sighs and gasps]
Uh
uh
audio routing cable. No,
I mean it's fine I guess if it's silent,
right?
Uh
there is a auto hotkey
uh script for this.
I can make it think I am focused on it.
that way. There is still audio,
but I'm worried if I get cuz this is a
this game has esports and stuff
apparently,
competitions and stuff. So, I'm like
thinking like
is it safe for me to do that?
I know.
Um
we p
How about that?
Let me do something. One second.
Okay. Wait.
Uh,
how do I
Oh shit. Wait, how do I run this?
Uh,
loading. Okay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. I fixed it. Oh my
god. Okay. Auto hotkey. Thank you. So,
I'm I'm literally not focused on the
game, but
uh the game thinks I'm focused on it,
but I'm not. That way you can you guys
on stream can hear the audio. It
wouldn't sound like I'm all tabbing.
That is nice.
That is actually nice.
We figured out something. He
get qui.
Uh, no.
Uh. Oh, full screen doesn't work. Oh,
isn't this like a old game?
So for [music] screen optimization when
Oh yeah, that will
is it me or when I put it on 1080p
the stuff looks blurry.
Or is it just me? Why does the text and
everything looks blurry?
Hey,
Wait, am I?
Yeah, this is clear. This is clear.
Clear. Clear. Okay,
watch this.
[snorts]
Hey, switch to this. It's start going to
start becoming blurry. Okay.
See, it's blurry.
It wor.
And why?
Why though?
Hey, why does it do that?
Hey,
wait. Alt enter. No, no, wait.
Wait, wait, wait. What was the command?
Control enter. No, hold
alt enter.
Ah, it forces forced.
Hey, why is it blurry though?
Why is it blurry though?
Oh, that is so weird.
If it's blurry like this, can't I like
go to in game files and like
uh is it not something like that? No,
nothing
like config something. Uh no. Okay, it
doesn't have it.
Yeah.
Yep. They do not have it, it seems.
Why was same games?
Oh, [snorts]
usually it's supposed to be there in the
save folder or something.
Uh,
I can't find it.
Wait, Sega, right? So, let's see.
Oh, it's over here. Wow.
What the
local?
Oh, it's Sega S
or P Pew Pew.
Oh, yes.
Config
file. Okay.
With the game just Okay.
Okay. Graphics config. [music]
Oh,
[sighs] okay. Okay. So, what it'll do is
1920 by
full screen one go one full screen width
of V6 one and uh
save this and
save this and right click and
mark as read Finally apply
quit to desktop
and I'll launch the game again.
And it should now give me uh 1080p
quality on a window at full screen
if I'm correct.
Yes.
Oh my god, I'm a genius.
No, it's not nothing about genius or
anything. It's just what it is there out
there for other games.
See, it's not blurry anymore. The boxes.
All right, there is a little bit of
blurriness. You see the ones over here?
One, one X.
Oh no. Is it that blurry?
It's not that blurry.
It's not that blurry, so it's fine.
Anyone know?
Uh let's uh
let us
wrap up. I guess
I can't
for tonight.
It is late.
Titan.
Uh I
will continue in the next  PP stream.
Okay.
Uh let me switch to the game scene. I
know talking scene.
My nose is blocked. Oh god, I've been
sneezing.
on stream and off stream. We have about
while muted the I muted the mic and was
sneezing so much.
It is
but yeah. Um
I I just want to say that like I
I'll be streaming more of this game. I
need to get used to
um used to the game and learn how to do
the uh chains and everything.
Uh, that would mean I have to use my
brain a lot,
but it's a fun game. It gives you like a
uh
it may it trains your brain to think
which colors can which pattern can go
well with this. Why? How should you
place the placement of the block? Uh the
pu or blocks. It's literally Tetris you
can say. Yeah. The more I play this
game, I feel like I should
try to play by one day play sandress
or something. There's a sand tress
thingy that's  also similar like this.
It's fun.
You can
uh you know match the colors and
make them
chain attack all those stuff.
Same stuff like neutralization and quick
quick move quick
stuff like that. I just really
interesting.
Um,
forgot my phone notifications.
Yeah,
a second.
Uh,
but yeah, today was fun. And I
got to
try out this game finally. Apparently
now uh everyone who are participating in
the tournament from India uh most of
them it's the game is like 250
rupees or something because of the 50%
off going on for this game on Steam for
the autumn sale.
So, since I'm in Japan, due to a
regional difference, uh the tournament
organizers organizers, they uh tried to
send me the free game copy cuz I'm a
participant, but they couldn't gift me.
I couldn't accept the gift because of
the regional thingy.
Apparently, if you didn't know, like on
Steam, they do allow cross region
gifting, but the issue is more like
if a game has regional restrictions.
For example,  this game is from Sega,
right? Yeah. So, Sega had regional
restrictions for this game. That's why
um
it it defaulted uh the Steam uh yeah if
a game publisher has regional uh
limitations
uh restrictions like that it will
default
back to the old thingy. Uh so you cannot
do cross gifting
or something. That's what let me when I
asked like
to in Google search it just said me that
apparently someone talked about this in
like for other games and also some
somewhere in Reddit I guess. I'm not
sure but yeah that happened. So, I was
given like a gift card,
the 640 yen gift card since in uh this
game in Japan is like 720
yen.
That's like in Indian rupees that's like
around
500 [music]
600 rupees
double the amount of what you are able
to buy fro インドでは250ルピーくらいで買える。
[鼻を鳴らす] なんで日本円ってこんなに
高いんだろう。でも、私にはよくわからない
。 過度に。
今日、
私の部屋で自転車が動かなくなったんだけど、
後輪がパンクしてたんだ。たぶん、
パンクか何かだと思うんだけど、
日本ではタイヤやチューブを交換するだけで6,000円もかかるんだ。
インドとかで
タイヤやチューブを交換する必要があるなら
、
2,000円か1,000円以下で済むのにね。  1000未満。   それ以上は
上がらないだろう。
6,000円は文字通り
3.7ルピーで、
切り上げて3,700
ルピーとします。   信じられないよ
。 いいえ、
サービス料として約7,000円かかりました。 そうそう。
馬鹿げたサービス料だ。 ええ、4,300
ルピーです。 信じられないよ。 クレイジー。   何と
言っていいかわからない。
ここは何もかも高いですね。
ああ、私の息子たちも。   やってくる
。
私はもっ​​と静かにしなければならない。
私が
もっと静かにしないといけないので、ルームメイトは寝ています。
うん。   ええと、そうですね
、
明日何を配信するかは皆さんにお知らせします。 それでは、また
。
本日はありがとうございました。 えっと、あぁ
、鼻が詰まってる。 息苦しい。 なんてこった
？
ええ、でも
私の鼻も詰まってます。 ああ、神様。
私の声を聞けばわかるはずです。 ああ、神様。
うん、でもああ
、鼻が詰まってる。 ああ、神様。
ああ、神様。
息ができない。 うん。
ねえ、インターネットが壊れかけているよ。
インターネット。
ああ、またインターネットが壊れた。
私は生放送中ですか？
ええ、あなたたちは2
分遅れています。
さて、そろそろ終わりにしようと思います
。 すみません、くしゃみが止まらないんです。   はい
、ここで締めくくりたいと思います。
くしゃみが頻繁に出る。
待って。
ああ、これは悪化している。
くしゃみが止まらない。 ええ、そうですね。
私の神について語らせてください。   わかった
。 ああ、神様、言葉も出ないよ。
彼が話すたびに、口を開けると、
くしゃみが出てしまう。   わかった
。 本日お越しいただいた皆様、改めてありがとうございました
。 皆さんのお名前を読み上げます。
ありがとう、ビクター。
ありがとう、アラサ。 ありがとう。
ありがとう。
マヤさん、来てくれてありがとう。
それから、えっと、アリサン、来てくれてありがとう
。 ロアン、来てくれてありがとう。
お越しいただきありがとうございます。
そして、
YouTubeやTwitter
やRumbleで潜伏していたすべての古い潜伏者。
配信をご覧いただき、本当にありがとうございました。 それは本当に本当に大きな
意味があります。
うん。 さよなら。
喉がひどく痛む。   というわけで
、改めて、
お越しいただきありがとうございました。 次回もまた配信します
。  Discord、
Twitter、Instagramのストーリーなどでお知らせします
。 ええ、そうですね。
こんにちは。
えっと、私、具合が悪いみたいです。
薬を飲まなければならない。 うーん、これはまずい。 天候は
ますます寒くなってきている。 ええ、
冬は嫌いだけど、いいところもある。
でも、風邪をひくのは本当に嫌だ。
温かいお湯とか飲めたよ。
ああ、これは本当にひどい。 ええ、でも
、改めてありがとうございました。
皆さん、良い一日を。 良い夜をお過ごしください。
バイバイ。
坊や、私の息子